RESUME

Yasmeen Sultana Email: smnkhan8@gmail.com

H/NO:-Plot NO. 8/S, Road NO.10/C Mobile:-8121011808

Jubilee Hills, Gayathri Hills Colony, Hyderabad-500045

Career Objective

To be associated with an organization that gives me scope to apply my knowledge and skills in accordance with the latest trends in an industry. To find a position as front desk agent where I can utilize my knowledge and experience in achieving the goal.

WORK EXPERIENCE: B2B SALES PROFESSIONAL

- Comfotel Hotel Assistant Sales Manager Dated: Jan 2017 to Dated: -Nov 2018 (19 months)
- Serene Nest Hotels & Apartment Sr. Sales Executive Dated :Feb 2016 to Date : dec 2016 (1 year)
- Menarva hotel Madhapur Sales Executive- Dated: Jan 2015 to Dec 2015 (1 year)

Sales Responsibilities:

- Identifying buyer's persona and executing lead generation campaign (Email marketing)
- Setting up in-person meetings with decision makers through cold-calling.
- Working closely with the business head to identify the target audience and engagement them
- Meeting revenue targets and promoting customer loyalty through prospect engagement.

WORK EXPERIENCE: GUEST RELATION EXPERT

- Hotel Trident Oberoi Sr. Executive, Guest Relations Dated: March 2014 to Dec 2014.
- Hotel Avasa Sr. Executive, Guest Relations- Dated: May 2013 to Oct 2013.
- Daspalla hotel Started as a Executive Guest Relations and transitioned to Sales co-ordinator-Dated: Oct 2011 to April 2013.
- Oyster Hotel Executive Guest Relations Dated: Jan 2010 to Aug 2011.
- Luxor Inn Hotel Executive Guest Relations Dated: Feb 2008 to Dec 2009.
- Apex Reception Manager Dated: Jan 2007 to Jan 2008.

Responsibility Sales:-

- Ensuring the Hotel sales department is always prepared for business.
- Visiting clients as well as entertaining them within the hotel.
- Actively promoting and selling the hotels bedrooms and facilities.

- Responding to guest concerns, questions and problems.
- Soliciting corporate rate business from business travel agents.
- Building and developing strong relationships with both new and old customers.
- Promoting the conference facilities that the hotel has to offer.
- Getting feedback from guests who are leaving and then drawing conclusions from it.
- Actioning all sales leads.
- Putting together sales reports and then forwarding those on to senior managers.
- Carrying out any reasonable requests as required by the General Manager.
- Keeping departmental costs in line with agreed annual budgets.
- Working within the local markets to promote our hotels to corporate clients.

EDUCATION:

- Degree Indira Gandhi National Open University (IGNOU) people's university B.A English 3year (Correspondence). Diploma in Hospitality Management
- SSC Matriculate From Board of secondary education, Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh.

COMPUTER SKILLS:-

- I have been trained in computer usability and operating, Hence comfortable to handle the assigned task in this field.
- Operating System: Ms Office & DTP.

LINGUISTIC ABILITY:-Has the ability to interact people in following languages:-

- English
- Hindi
- Telugu

STRENGTH:

- Communication and organizational skill
- Professional attitude
- Time management skills
- Ability to speak several languages.

HOBBIES:

- Mehndi designs and drawing.
- Professional Networking thru Professional Networking Portals.

PERSONAL PROFILE;-

Name :- Yasmeen sultana

Father Name :-Sayeed khan

Nationality :- Indian

Religion :- Muslim

Birth Date :-11/MAY/1989

Marital Status :- Single

Date: 17/04/16

Place: Hyderabad (Yasmeen sultana)